交易都在十字路口做  咒语很厉害
Crossroads are where packs are made, serious spell work.
那就跟恶魔有关了
I means it got something to do with demons.
这些人竟然跟恶魔做交易
These people are actually making deals with the damned thing.
他们看到的是地狱之犬  恶魔的斗牛犬
They're seeing hellhounds -- demonic pit bulls.
你能控制他们
You can control them?
去咬他
Sic him, boy!
盖思终于把他们带到了他的船屋
Garth finally got them to his houseboat,
但凯文读他们手里那半块石碑并不顺利
but Kevin's having a lot of trouble reading their half of the tablet.
-门口那是什么东西  -巫尘
- So, what is that stuff out front? - Goofer dust.
你们两个自以为了不起
You boys think you know something about something,
却连巫尘都不知道
but not goofer dust?
-是什么东西  -巫术
- What is it? - Hoodoo.
阻挡恶魔的
Keeps out demons.
盒子里有一把钥匙
In the box is the key
能找到一切  卷轴  咒语
to every object, scroll, spell,
几千年来收集的所有东西
ever collected for thousands of years
都放在一个地方
under one roof.
简直是超自然知识的金矿
It is the supernatural mother lode.
如果知识是力量
If knowledge is power,
那这就是世界上最有威力的地方
then this is the most powerful place on earth.
如今
阿司匹林
我去
Holy crap.
我去啊
Holy crap!
该死
Holy crap.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十四集
反复测试
你好啊  妈妈
Hey, mom.
不赖啊
Not bad.
不赖
"Not bad"?
我从来没有过自己的房间
I haven't had my own room...
从来没有
Ever.
这简直棒呆了
I'm making this awesome.
我有超棒的唱片
I've got my kickass vinyl.
还有妙不可言的床垫
I've got this killer mattress.
记忆棉的  它还能记住我
Memory foam -- it remembers me.
还是干净的  没有怪味
And it's clean, too. There's no funky smell.
不像汽车旅馆有些吓人的污渍
There's no creepy motel stains.
不是吧
Really?
抱歉
Sorry.
我去弄点吃的
I'm gonna go fix us some grub.
看什么呢
What you reading?
什么都读
Sort of, uh, everything.
好啊
Oh, good.
总得有人把这些都读一读
Somebody's gonna have to dig through all this,
那人肯定不是我
and it ain't gonna be me.
这是你做的
You made these?
我们现在有厨房了
We have a real kitchen now.
我知道  我只是以为你不知道厨房为何物
I know. I-I just didn't think you knew what a kitchen was.
我要在这儿安顿下来了
I'm nesting, okay?
吃你的吧
Eat.
不错吧
Huh? Yeah.
不客气
You're welcome.
说
Yo.
迪恩  快来
Dean? Come quick.
怎么了
What?
凯文
Kevin?
Kevin?!
出事了吗
Something wrong?
你猜呢
Guess.
凯文  是我们
Kevin? It's us.
找到他了
Found him.
你气色真是糟透了
Wow. You look like hammered crap.
是啊
Yeah.
-你还睡觉吗  -不怎么睡
- Are you sleeping? - Not really.
你吃东西了吗
Are you eating?
基本上是吃热狗
Hot dogs, mostly.
是啊  最佳早餐了
Sure, yeah -- breakfast of champions.
我这么说都觉得不好意思
Look, I'm gonna feel dirty saying this,
但你该吃点沙拉再洗个澡
but you might want a salad and a shower.
我知道  我一直头疼又流鼻血
I know, and I've been getting bad headaches and nosebleeds,
我好像还小小地中风了一次
and I think maybe I had a small stroke.
但这都是值得的
But it was worth it.
值得什么
What was worth it?
我知道怎么关闭地狱之门了
I figured out how to close the gates of hell.
你
You --
过来抱抱  你个臭小子
Come here, you smelly son of a bitch.
那这是什么个情况
Okay, okay. So, what does this mean?
-到底是什么东西  -是个咒语
- What are we looking at? - It's a spell.
然后呢
And?
只是几句天使语
And it's just a few words of enochian, but...
看看
Oh, here we go.
每次说出咒语之前
...the spell has to be spoken
都得先通过测试[庭审]  共有三道咒
after you finish each of the three trials.
庭审  《法律与秩序》那种吗
T-trials like, uh, like "Law & order"?
过五关斩六将那种
More like Hercules.
石碑上说  "决定担此重任之人
The tablet says, "Whosoever chooses to undertake these tasks
必须不惧危险  死亡
should fear not danger, nor death, nor..."
还有一个词貌似是把你的脊椎
A word I think means getting your spine ripped out
从你嘴里扯出来
through your mouth for all eternity.
好啊
Good times.
总体来说  上帝建立了一系列测试
Basically, God built a series of tests,
等你都完成了  就可以去关门了
and when you've done all three, you can slam the gates.
怎么  上帝想让我们参加高考吗
So, what, God wants us to take the SATs?
差不多吧  上帝的意旨深不可测
I-I guess. Uh, he works in mysterious ways.
是啊  深不可测的混蛋
Yeah, mysterious, douche-y ways.
好吧  第一项是什么
All right. Where do we start?
目前我只破解出一项测试
I've only been able to crack one of the tests so far,
而且挺恶心的
and it's gross.
你得杀一只地狱之犬并浸于它的血中
You've got to kill a hound of hell and bathe in its blood.
棒极了
Awesome.
这有什么棒的
Awesome?
当然了
Yeah.
如果能干掉所有的恶魔
Hey, if this means icing all demons,
我完全不介意杀条恶魔狗
I got no problem gutting some devil dog
再淋上他的鲜血
and letting Calgon take me away.
你们上哪去找啊
Where are you gonna find one?
地狱之犬总去收恶魔交易的账
Well, hellhounds like to collect on crossroads deals.
我们只要找到一个十年前
So all we got to do is track down some loser
为了某件事而做了交易的家伙
who signed over his special sauce 10 years ago,
然后拦下一只冲着他去的地狱之犬
get between him and Clifford the big dead dog --
轻松
Easy.
听起来并不轻松
Doesn't sound easy.
的确不轻松
It's not.
你去网上查查看
Look, you get on the net -- see what you can dig up.
我去买东西  我们需要巫尘
I'm gonna go for a supply run because we need goofer dust,
而且这孩子需要吃点
and the kid needs to eat something
长蹄子的动物和猪菊花以外的东西
that's not ground-up hooves and pigs' anuses --
倒不是说那样有什么不好
not that there's anything wrong with that.
我感觉好多了
Okay, I feel a lot better.
凯文  伙计  你得悠着点
Hey, Kevin, buddy, you got to slow down.
什么
What?
去睡一觉
Get some shut-eye.
休息一天
Take a day off.
开开窗
Open a window.
不行
No.
你说要干掉地狱  那样我才能出去
You said nuking hell -- that's how I get out.
那样我才能回家
That's how I go home.
没错  但你不能这么生活
Right, it is, but you can't live like this.
你以为我愿意吗
You think I want to?
我也讨厌这里
I hate it here.
但是这世上的每个恶魔都想杀了我
I can't leave because every demon on the planet
所以我不能离开
wants to peel my face off.
除了你们  偶尔过来的盖思还有我妈妈
I can't talk to anyone except you guys or Garth,
我不能接触别人
when he swings by, or my mom.
她打电话来也只是哭
Right? And when she calls, all she does is cry.
我只是...
I just...
我想结束这件事
I need this to be over.
这我懂
I know. I do.
但你得听我一句
But trust me on this --
拯救世界这档子事
This whole "saving the world" thing --
是个马拉松  不是短跑
it's a marathon, not a sprint.
你得好好照顾自己
You got to take better care of yourself.
你知道西红柿有六千种吗
Did you know that there are, like, 6,000 kinds of tomatoes?
查到什么了吗
Did you find anything?
是的  十年前恶魔的形迹
Yeah, demon signs, 10 years ago,
中心点在爱达荷州  肖松尼
all centered on Shoshone, Idaho.
动静越大  恶魔来头越大
Okay, well, big-time mojo means a big-time freak.
那儿有谁撞大运了吗
So, anybody have a horseshoe shoved up his ass?
可以这么说
That's one way of putting it.
这是卡西迪一家  本是小农民
Meet the Cassitys, small-time farmers
03年2月却在自家地里挖到了油
who struck oil on their land in February of '03,
奇怪的是  地理勘探显示...
which is weird because geological surveys --
你说"奇怪"就够了
Yeah, you had me at "weird."
好吧  这是交易吗
All right. We thinking deal?
这是最佳线索了
Best lead we've got.
去见见这些新土豪吧
Well, let's go visit the Beverly Hillbillies.
你留下继续研究第二项测试
You stay here, work on step number 2,
如果看到什么跟地狱之犬有关的东西
and, uh, if you come across anything about hellhounds,
跟我们说一声
drop a dime, okay?
因为那些东西又是利爪  尖牙
'cause between the -- the claws and the teeth
又是隐形什么的  所以他们
and the whole invisibility thing, those bitches can be...
挺不好对付的
real bitches.
我给你买了礼物
I got you a present.
蓝色的是治头疼的
The, uh, blue ones are for the headaches,
绿色的让你有精神
and the greens are for pep.
别服过量了
Don't O.D.
谢谢
Thanks?
这样好吗
You sure about that?
萨姆  现在离成功只有一步了
Sam, we are on the one-yard-line.
我们得死撑下去
It is time to play through the pain.
卡西迪牧场
爱达荷州  肖松尼
好了  留心点
All right, keep an eye out.
被地狱之犬盯上的人
Anybody with a hellhound on their ass
肯定会表露出来
is gonna be showing signs --
看到幻象  惊恐不已什么的
hallucinating, freaking out -- the usual.
如果找到了呢
And if we find someone?
你把他们引开
You get 'em clear.
我去干掉他们
I spike fido.
皆大欢喜
The crowd goes wild.
伙计  这里谁管事
Hey, pal, who runs this joint?
我
You're looking at her.
你是农场主
You...own the ranch?
不  只是打理而已
Nope, just manage the property.
你们是来找活儿干的吗
You guys here about the job?
怎么猜到的
How'd you guess?
我们这儿来过不少到处漂的
We get our share of drifters.
你们在农场干过吗
Ever worked a farm before?
当然了
Definitely.
我们学得很快
We're quick learners.
艾莉  这是谁啊
Ellie...who we got here?
我是迪恩  这是萨姆
I'm Dean. This is Sam.
卡尔・格兰维尔  幸会
Carl Granville. A pleasure.
幸会  你不是卡西迪家的人
Pleasure. So you're not a Cassity?
不  内人是
No, my wife is.
这是他们家的财产
Her and her family own the place.
我就是个  怎么说来着
I'm just one those, uh -- what you call 'em? --
奖杯丈夫
trophy husbands.
一般是说"奖杯妻子"  尤指特别漂亮的妻子
我们要雇他们吗
So, we, uh, hiring the fellas?
还没想好
Not sure yet.
雇吧  他们看起来挺不错
Oh, come on. They seem like swell guys.
是啊  我们挺不错的
Well, he's right. We're swell.
你们的床在这边
You bed down in here.
五点早饭  八点晚饭
Breakfast is at 5:00, dinner is at 8:00,
在那之间  都听我使唤
And in between, you're mine.
有什么问题吗
Questions?
我怀念我的房间
I miss my room.
没问题
We're good.
好吧  如果你们愿意就可以雇你们
Okay. Job is yours if you want it.
但得提醒你们一句  活儿挺累的[屎]
But I better warn you -- it's crap work.
屎  原来真是屎的意思
Crap -- she literally meant crap.
我恨你
I hate you.
我不管  你觉得我像个嬉皮士吗
I don't care. Do I look like a hippie?
有机食物对牛更好
Organic food is better for the cattle.
我的地  我的牲畜  我的钱  我说了算
My land, my animals, my money, my way -- end of story.
她还挺厉害啊
She's a real piece of work, huh?
爱丽丝・卡西迪是挺"厉害"的
Alice Cassity's a piece of something, all right?
但是也没办法  她是老板
But what are we gonna do? She's the boss.
喝一杯
Drink?
你怎么看
So, what are we thinking?
你说交易的事吗
What, dealwise?
艾莉只是雇员  她肯定排除
Well, Ellie's the help, so that rules her out.
卡尔看上去不像出卖灵魂的人
And Carl doesn't really seem like the sell-your-soul type.
是爱丽丝吗
So, Alice?
猜中了
Ding-ding-ding.
去跟她谈谈
Should we talk to her?
好让对我们撒谎  再去报警吗  不
Why? So she can lie to us and then call the cops? No.
不  这次我们跟住她就行  萨姆
No, we're gonna have to go stalker on this one, Sammy.
-整匹马吗  -是啊
- The whole horse? - Oh, yes.
-不是吧  -是啊
- Seriously? - Yes.
她怎么
What does she --
是只狼吧
Just a wolf.
是啊
Yeah.
大概把马都吓坏了
Probably spooked the hell out of the horses.
我去看看他们
I should check on them.
好啊  快点回来
Well, all right. Hurry back.
好的
Okay.
不
No!
老天啊
God almighty.
我很遗憾艾莉  卡尔看上去人不错
I'm sorry, Ellie. Carl seemed like a good guy.
他最好了
The best.
他的头被扯下来了吗
You say his head was practically ripped off?
你是
And you are?
好奇而已
Just curious.
他是新来的工人
He's new. He works here.
卡尔死状很惨  其他的别多说了
Carl died bad -- let's leave it at that.
这里又引入了几匹狼
They've been reintroducing wolves 'round these parts,
-但是我没想到  -这不是狼干的
- but I never thought... - This wasn't a wolf.
我得去打电话了
I got to make some phone calls.
他们一家人都会乘飞机赶来
The whole family's flying in for this.
卡西迪一家团聚
All the Cassitys under one roof.
祝你好运
Good luck.
该死
Oh, son of a bitch.
你怎么看
So, what do you think?
我看卡尔做了交易  所以被狗吃了
I think Carl signed the deal, and now he's dog food.
如今狗没了
Hellhound's gone,
而我们当时跟错了人  没能阻止他们
and we were too busy chasing a pile of jack to stop it.
我们拿上东西走人吧
Let's grab our stuff and get out of here.
卡西迪太太  你还好吧
You okay, Mrs. Cassity?
我没事
Fine.
真的吗
You sure?
真的没事
I really am.
我知道我应该很难过  因为我爱卡尔
And...I know I shouldn't be because I loved Carl...
或许是吧
I think.
我只是记不住为什么会爱上他了
I just can't remember why.
什么意思
What do you mean?
卡尔是在这儿长大的
I mean... Carl grew up around here.
我们是同学  他一直倾心于我
We went to school together, and he was always mooning over me.
但我从没...我以前还取笑过他
But I never -- I used to make fun of him.
你们什么时候在一起的
When did you two get together?
03年的情人节
Valentine's day, 2003.
我去了一个派对
I was at this party.
卡尔也去了
Carl was there,
感觉就像我第一次看到了他
and it was like i was seeing him for the first time.
他突然变得帅气  聪明  风趣
You know, suddenly he was cute and smart and funny.
感觉很奇妙
It was magic.
卡尔和我幸福地生活了十年
Carl and I were happy for 10 years.
现在他死了  我既不悲伤也不生气
Now he's dead, and I'm not sad or angry.
我什么事都没有
I'm just...fine.
我们有墓地的土吗
Hey, we, uh, we have any graveyard dirt?
应该有吧  怎么了
We should. Why?
蓍草
Yarrow?
有  不行
Yeah. No.
迪恩  不行
Dean, no.
我们不能召唤十字路口恶魔
We're not summoning a crossroads demon.
第一计划没成功  只能用备用计划了
Plan "A" bombed, so welcome to plan "B" --
我们抓个红眼恶魔
We get some red-eyed bitch in a trap,
我们拿刀抵着她
then we hold a knife on her
直到她召唤条狗来
until she calls us in a pooch --
就像快递
special delivery.
但如果克劳力知道我们自己找上门了
Yeah, except when Crowley finds out we're dialing up hell,
他就不会派一只地狱之犬了  而是一百只
he won't send one hellhound -- he'll send a hundred.
这不叫计划  迪恩  这叫自杀
That's not a plan, Dean -- that's suicide.
你有更好的主意吗
Well, you got a better idea?
有  我们留下
Yeah, we stay here.
我刚刚在谷仓里跟爱丽丝谈话
I just talked to Alice in the barn.
卡尔出卖灵魂不是为了石油
Carl didn't sell his soul for oil --
而是为了爱丽丝
he sold it for Alice.
他老婆
His wife?
他爱她  而她却没注意过她
He loved her, she barely noticed him,
所以他就做了交易
so he made a deal.
如今时间一到
And now that time's up,
她觉得自己甚至不认识他了
it's like she barely even knew the guy.
你觉得这个恶魔在镇上的时候
You think our demon signed up more than one schmuck
不止做了一笔交易
while he was in town?
也不是第一次了
Wouldn't be the first time.
迪恩  这家人能富起来
Look, Dean, this family's rich
是因为有人订了张直达地狱的票
because someone booked a one-way ticket downstairs.
而明天  他们都会到这儿
And as of tomorrow, they're all gonna be right here.
你想把他们审一遍
And you want to scope 'em out?
我想杀条地狱之犬  还不用送命
I want to kill a hellhound and not die.
你呢
How 'bout you?
两天  然后按我的方法来
Two days -- then we do it my way.
这是诺亚・卡西迪
Meet Noah Cassity.
71岁  十亿身价
He's 71, worth a billion,
刚娶了第五任妻子  20岁的内衣模特
And just married wife number 5, a 20-year-old lingerie model.
因为共同语言吗
'cause they have so much in common?
爱丽丝是长女  那是辛迪  二女儿
Alice is his oldest, and that's Cindy, the middle girl.
几年前她的一张专辑上过乡村音乐榜
She had a single on the country chart a few years ago.
之后她开始酗酒
Then she started hitting the bottle,
然后就
and, well...
她最后一张专辑是以狗为主题的节日歌曲
Her last album was a bunch of holiday songs for dogs.
我最喜欢的是《铃儿吠叮当》
My favorites were "Jingle bark rock"
和《别在这棵树上撒尿:植树节快乐》
and "Don't pee on this tree: happy arbor day."
她是恶魔喽
So she's the devil.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
那个是小女儿  玛格特
And there's the baby -- Margot.
她在爱丽丝和卡尔结婚之前离家了
She ran away just before Alice and Carl tied the knot,
住在巴黎
lives in Paris.
你怎么知道的
How do you know all this?
我从13岁就开始在这儿工作了
I've been working on this farm since I was 13,
而且我长眼睛了
and I've got eyes.
今晚需要全员出动
Okay, tonight is an all-hands-on-deck situation.
你们有一个人得在屋里
I'm gonna need one of you inside,
端盘子  倒酒
serving dinner and pouring drinks --
倒很多酒
a lot of drinks.
你好好玩吧  我就不等你了
Okay. Well, have fun. I won't wait up.
还得有人去烤肉
And somebody's gonna man the grill.
什么样的烤肉
What kind of grill?
不赖吧
Impressed?
我喜欢能烤肉的男人
I do like a man who can handle his meat.
不是吧
Really?
继续倒吧  伙计
Keep it coming, Ken Doll.
你最好了  艾莉
You're the best, Ellie.
爱尔  卡尔的事我真难过
Al, I'm so sorry about Carl.
他可是你的挚爱啊
I mean, he was the love of your life.
是啊
Right.
得了  她能找更好的
Please, she can do better.
或许爱丽丝该找个小孩结婚
Maybe Alice should marry a child --
像她父亲那样
take after her father.
-伊凡卡不是孩子  -是啊
- Ivanka's not a child. - Right.
她是个娃娃脸的妓女
She's a prostitute who looks like a child.
你们说完了没  爱丽丝还在服丧
Are you done? Alice is in mourning.
抱歉  玛姬
Oh, I'm sorry, Margie.
我没看到你  你谁都瞧不起  都飘上天了
I didn't see you there -- you're too far up on your high horse.
是啊  你说得对
Oh, yes, but you are right --
我们该停一下  为卡尔说几句话
We should all take a minute and say a few words about Carl.
你先来
You first.
他床上功夫好吗
Was he a good lay?
什么
What?
你不知道吗
Oh, you didn't know?
爸爸曾看到他们在谷仓里搞起
Yeah, daddy caught 'em going at it in the barn.
爱尔  那是你们俩在一起之前
Al, it was before you two got together.
卡尔他爱你
I mean, Carl -- he loved you.
是啊  那是玛姬还是个胖妞
Yeah, that was back when Margie was fat
辛还没酗酒的时候
and Cin was sober,
很久之前了
a long time ago.
得癌症死掉吧  老头子
Get cancer and die, old man.
你先请  亲爱的
You first, sweetie.
他们一直是这样吗
Are they always like this?
差不多吧
More or less.
你怎么在这儿干得下去
How can you work here?
我喜欢这块地  我喜欢动物
I love the property, I love the animals,
不去理会那些人
and I tune out the people.
我都记不住上次我们
Well, I can't remember the last time
坐在一起吃饭是什么时候了
we all sat down and had a meal together.
是在那个破旧的老房子
It was back at the old, crappy house,
爸爸请那个旅行推销员来家吃饭
when daddy invited that traveling salesman to dinner.
是啊
Oh, him.
他那么有魅力
He was so charming.
还是英国人
Yeah, English.
他叫什么来着  肯尼
What was his name -- Kenny?
克劳...
Crow-- crow--
Crowl-- crowl--
-克劳力  -克劳力
- Crowley? - Crowley.
-克劳力  -他们是这么说的
- Crowley? - That's what they said.
显然他十年前曾经来过这里
Apparently, he swung through town 10 years ago, to the day.
你觉得是他订下了这些交易
So, what -- do you think tea and crumpets made these deals
现在来收账了
and now he's collecting?
或者只是派狗来  让他们去收
Or he just sent his dog -- told it to go fetch.
那家伙可是地狱之王
Dude's king of hell.
自己出马不是太屈尊了
Grabbing a few souls -- that's got to be below his pay grade.
是吧  知道是谁做的交易了吗
I guess. Any idea who signed the dotted line?
完全不知道
I have no clue.
他们互不相让
It's brutal in there.
凯文  什么事
Hey, Kev, what's up?
迪恩  好消息  算是吧
Hey, Dean, good news, uh, I think...kind of.
别吹过头了
Don't oversell it.
抱歉
Sorry.
我在石碑上找到点东西  关于地狱之犬的
Um, I found something on the tablet, uh, about hellhounds.
不知道有没有用
Uh, this mean anything to you --
只有受诅咒之人  或透过圣火烤过的物体
"The dire creatures may be seen only by the damned
才能看到这些可怕的生灵
or through an object scorched with holy fire"?
你是说圣油吗
Like with holy oil?
必须的
It's got to be.
我们可以用窗户
We could use a window.
或是眼镜
Or glasses.
我们后备箱好像还有点圣油
I think we've still got some jesus juice left in the trunk.
我去弄那个X光设备
All right, I'll take care of the, uh, the x-ray specs.
你留下
You stay here.
死死盯住这些人
Do not let J.R. and the gang out of your sight, all right?
好的  凯文  你干的漂亮
Right. Hey, Kevin, uh, you did great, man.
去睡觉吧
Get some sleep.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Tha--
瞧  爸爸喝醉了  还带着武器
Oh, look. Daddy's drunk and armed.
肯定到圣诞节了
Must be Christmas.
你们去哪
Where are you going?
我乐意去哪去哪
Wherever I damn well please.
那只狼杀了我女婿
The wolf that killed my son-in-law --
吃人的畜生应该宰了他
He's a man-eater, got to be put down.
这是为了卡尔
Doing this for Carl.
你们先等一下
Okay, just -- just hold on a second.
不  这就去
No, going now.
我跟你们一起去
I'll come with you.
你会打猎吗
You know anything about hunting, boy?
略知一二
A little bit, yeah.
那我们去吧
Let's do it.
我喜欢
I like it...
你很像克拉克・肯特[超人]
...the whole Clark Kent look.
艾莉
Ellie, hey.
那么
So...
我觉得你很帅
I think you're really hot.
想去我房间  滚床单吗
You want to go to my room and have sex?
什么
What?
抱歉
I -- sorry.
我一般不这样
I don't usually do this.
我大概是太兴奋了
I guess I'm feeling my oats.
我不能
I can't.
什么
What?
好吧
Okay.
我现眼了
Uh, embarrassing.
不不  我想的
Oh, no, no, no. No, I want to.
超级想
Believe me.
没关系  不用照顾我
No, it's okay -- you don't.
我还是
I guess I'm gonna...
艾莉
Ellie, um...
改天
Rain check?
过期不候
This is one night only.
抱歉
Sorry.
小心点  孩子
Watch yourself, boy.
玛姬呢
Where's Margie?
我还以为她跟你在一起
I thought she was with you.
-天哪  -回屋里去
- Oh, my god! - Go back to the house.
-快去  -不
- Go! Move! - No!
那是什么玩意儿
What was that thing?
是地狱之犬
It was a hellhound.
把灵魂出卖给恶魔后
See, when you sell your soul to a demon,
它们就会来把你的灵魂扯出来
they're the ones that come and rip it out of you.
恶魔
Demon?
克劳力
Crowley.
很风骚的男人  大概这么高  超级大混蛋
Poncey guy, about yea big, mountain of dicks.
我们知道他十年前来过  帮人圆梦
We know he was here 10 years ago, making dreams come true.
如果你们没做交易  很好
Now, if you didn't sign, great.
外面那怪物就不会碰你
That freak out there won't touch you.
如果你们做了交易  现在就告诉我
But if you did, I need to know, and I need to know now.
举手吧
So, hands up.
等等
So, wait.
那个英国佬是恶魔
T-the British guy was a demon,
现在地狱之犬要来追杀我们
and now there's a hellhound after us?
你疯了吗
A-are you insane?
他们显然是疯了
They're obviously insane.
别装傻
Don't play dumb.
我才没有  我没出卖灵魂
Yeah. I'm not playing. I didn't sell my damn soul.
有人这么做了
Well, somebody did,
这个白痴早点承认
and the sooner that idiot owns up,
其他人就能早点离开
the sooner the rest of you can go.
-好了  把他们锁起来  -好
- All right, seal 'em in. - Yeah.
-什么  -我要把巫尘
- What?! - Look, I'm gonna spread goofer dust
撒在门窗边
around the doors, the windows.
能暂时把地狱之犬挡在外面
That will keep the hellhound out...for a while.
那是什么  能挡多久
What is that-- how long?
让我有机会一刀划开它的喉咙
Long enough for me to stab it in its throat.
不行  你不能这么做
No way. No way. You can't do this.
-你不能  -我能  想知道为什么吗
- You can't-- - Yes, I can. You want to know why?
因为我就是干这行的  而且我是最棒的
Because it's what I do. And, buddy, I'm the best.
我去杀了外面那条狗
See, I gut old yeller out there,
那么或许  你还有一线生机
and maybe-- just maybe-- you walk away.
我不这么做的话  你必死无疑
I don't-- you're meat.
坐下  闭嘴
So, sit down, shut up...
戴上手铐
and put these on.
我不...
I don't...
你们到底是谁
Who are you people?
我们是来帮忙的
We're here to help.
好像你们帮玛姬一样
Like you helped Margie?
地狱之犬靠近时
When the hellhound gets close,
你们也许会幻视  幻听
you might start seeing things, hearing things.
就像嗑药出现了不良反应
It's gonna feel like you took the brown acid,
折磨得你要死
and it's trying to kill you.
手铐是用来避免你们伤害自己的
The handcuffs are so you won't hurt yourselves.
等你们有谁瞪圆了眼睛
And when one of you starts bugging out,
就知道猎狗是冲着谁来的了
we'll know who's on tap to be puppy chow.
我们怎么办
So...what's our play?
你待在这里  找出是谁出卖了自己的灵魂
Well, you camp here, figure out who whored their soul.
我去外面看看
I'm gonna go scout the grounds --
看看能不能在它再次出击前杀了它
see if I can't gank huckleberry hound before he makes his next move.
等等  你不能自己去  迪恩
Wait, you're not going alone, Dean.
-我要跟你一起去  -不行
- I'm gonna come with you. - Wrong.
反正已经关着他们了  你需要人帮忙
Uh, they're on lockdown, and you need backup.
-我才不用  -你需要的
- No, I don't. - Yes, you do.
我要你安安全全的  萨姆
No, I need you to be safe, Sam, okay?
-这才是我要的  -什么
- That's what I need. - What?
我...我们什么时候真正安全过
What am I...when are we ever safe?
这次不一样
This is different.
怎么不一样
How?
因为那三项测试
Because of the three trials crap.
上帝的磨难考验
God's little obstacle course.
我们以前经历过这种事
We've been down roads like this before, man.
黄眼恶魔  路西法  迪克・罗曼
With yellow-eyes, Lucifer, Dick friggin' Roman.
我们都知道结局怎样  我们其中一个要牺牲
We both know where this ends...one of us dies...
或者更糟
or worse.
那又怎样  你决定你该去牺牲
So what, you just up and decided it's gonna be you?
我是个粗人  萨姆  你不是
I'm a grunt, Sam. You're not.
-你总是出主意的人  -迪恩
- You've always been the brains of this operation. - Dean...
而且你说过  你看见了一条出路
And you told me yourself that you see a way out.
你看到这糟糕生活还有希望
You see a light at the end of this ugly-ass tunnel.
但我没有
I don't.
告诉你我知道什么
But I tell you what I do know...
我会战死
It's that I'm gonna die with a gun in my hand.
因为那就是等着我的结局
Cause that's what I have waiting for me --
那是我唯一的结局
That's all I have waiting for me.
我想让你走出这一切
I want you to get out.
我想让你有一个生活
I want you to have a life...
成为记录者  什么都行
Become a man of letters, whatever.
找个老婆  生几个孩子  还有孙子
You, with a wife and kids and...and...and grandkids,
活到长胖  变秃  还有吃伟哥
Living till you're fat and bald and chugging viagra...
那才是我理想中的结局
That is my perfect ending,
也必须只有这一种结局
And it's the only one that I'm gonna get.
所以我要去做这些测试
So I'm gonna do these trials.
我要自己去做  就这样
I'm gonna do them alone, end of story.
你要待在这儿  我要出去
You're staying here. I'm going out there.
要是那东西来了  你打电话给我
If landshark comes knocking, you call me.
你要是想跟着我
If you try to follow me,
我就冲你的腿来一枪
I'm gonna put a bullet in your damn leg.
你出卖了你的灵魂  承认吧
You sold your soul, admit it.
你怎么会这样想
Why the hell would you think that?
因为你行将就木
'cause you're a walking corpse,
却娶了一个骚货
and you're married to a centerfold.
不难想象
I did the math.
她喜欢钱  我很有钱  怎么了
She likes money, and I'm rich. Do it again.
你唱歌吓死人  怎么上的榜单
You sing like crap, so explain the music career.
知道什么叫自动调音吗
Hello -- auto-tune!
好了  够了
All right. That's enough.
是吗  四眼怪  够了吗
Oh, is it, four-eyes? Is it enough?
你为什么会觉得我们有人做了恶魔交易
I don't know why you even think one of us made a deal.
因为你们在没有石油的地方找到了石油
Because you struck oil where there was no any oil.
你不觉得那很奇怪吗
That didn't seem weird to you?
玛姬
Margie.
玛姬以前常说
Margie used to say that...
如果我们有钱  我们就会很幸福
that if we were rich, we'd all be happy.
是啊  我们就是受诅咒的沃顿一家
Right. We're the damn Waltons.
《沃顿一家》是七十年代的一部剧集
来得正是时候
Just in time.
艾莉  你还好吗
Ellie, are you okay?
很好
I'm good.
我敢说你肯定很厉害
And I bet you're great.
的确  好极了
Yep, great.
好了
Okay.
听着
Listen...
好吧  无论发生什么  听到什么
Okay, whatever happens, whatever you hear,
你要待在这儿把门锁紧
You need to stay in here with that door locked.
别出去  好吗
Sit tight, okay?
这听起来会很疯狂
This is gonna sound crazy,
外面有非常邪恶的东西
but there is something evil out there.
我知道
I know.
你知道
You know?
它是冲着我来的
It's coming for me.
我要尿尿
I need to take a leak.
憋着
Hold it.
我这么大岁数能憋着吗
Yeah, at my age?
我可做不到
Not really an option,
你要么让我去  要么就给我个瓶子
so either you let me go or get me a bottle.
真恶心
You're disgusting.
等下
Wait!
不要
No!
不不  求你了
No, no, please.
让我走吧  求你了
Just let me go, please. Please.
不要
No!
求你不要伤害我的家人
Please, don't hurt my family.
我没有  我是在帮你们
I'm not. I'm trying to help you.
快进屋
Get in the house.
-什么  什么  -快去
- What? What? - Go!
-天哪  -快去
- Oh, god! - Go!
我父母离婚后  我妈来这儿工作
When my parents split up, my mom took a job here.
那是卡西迪家还没钱的时候
This was before the Cassitys had money,
但那是她能找到的最好的活儿了
but it was the best she could do.
所以我在这个农场长大
So I grew up on this farm.
你就是这么遇见克劳力的
That's how you met Crowley?
他们准备了一桌盛宴
They had this big dinner,
那之后  我看见他亲吻玛姬
and after, I saw him kissing Margie.
我跑走了  不知道该怎么办
I ran. I didn't know what to do.
但克劳力找到了我  聊了聊
But Crowley found me. We talked.
他表现得很和善
He seemed so nice.
技艺高超的骗子都这样
The best con men always do.
他问我  我最大的愿望是什么
He asked me, if I had one wish, what would it be?
我就告诉了他
So I told him.
他逼迫你卖了你的灵魂
And he made you sign over your soul.
他没有逼迫我做任何事
He didn't make me do anything.
我妈妈  她患了帕金森
My mom -- she had Parkinson's --
早期阶段  我知道她结局是什么
early stages, and I knew how that story would end.
所以我做了交易
So I took the deal.
我妈现在退休了  每天在凤凰城打高尔夫
Ma is retired down in Phoenix now, plays golf every day.
艾莉  那真是太蠢了
That was a stupid move, Ellie.
迪恩  我是为了妈妈才这么做的
I did it for my mom, Dean.
换做是你  你愿意为你妈妈做什么
What would you do for your mom?
你应该知道会有这一天
You had to know this was coming.
不  怎么可能知道
No. How?
克劳力没有告诉你有十年期限
Crowley didn't tell you about the 10-year ticking clock?
什么
What?
我只知道我死后去不了天堂
I knew that when I died, I wasn't going to heaven,
但他从没说过十年期限或者什么怪物
but he never said anything about that or monsters.
混蛋
What a douche bag.
大概他也没跟卡尔和玛格特说
He probably didn't say jack to Carl or Margot, either.
玛姬也做了交易
Margie made a deal?
那么她...
So she's...
她死了
She's gone.
天哪
Oh, god.
我
I...
几年前  卡尔喝得烂醉
A few years ago, Carl got drunk.
他告诉我他在一个十字路口施了魔法
He told me he did some kind of magic at a crossroads --
召唤了一个恶魔
Summoned a demon.
我把事情一联系起来
I put two and two together,
又看到那东西对他做的事...
and when I saw what that thing did to him...
但我不知道玛姬也这样
I just never knew about Margie.
我以为我才是下一个
I thought I was next.
-而你居然没逃走  -逃去哪
- And you didn't run? - Where would I run?
我只想吃好最后一顿
All I wanted was one last meal,
再听听优美的旋律  也许
some good tunes, and maybe...
我不想死
I don't want to die.
迪恩  怎么了
Dean, what's happening?
艾莉  你看到的都不是真的
Ellie, whatever you're seeing, it's not real.
这说明地狱之犬  就在附近
It means the hellhound -- it's close.
听好  你得待在这个圈里  明白吗
Look, you need to stay inside this circle, okay?
立刻进去
Now.
迪恩
Dean...
不论发生什么  你都不要出来
No matter what happens, you stay inside that circle.
明白吗
You understand me?
你就是克劳力的狗啊
Oh, so you're Crowley's bitch.
宠物还真像主人啊
I guess pets really do look like their owners.
你在等什么呢
What are you waiting for?
快上吧
Come and get it!
你得去医院
You need to go to a hospital.
这不算严重
Oh, I've had worse.
对  这话不假
Yeah, he's had worse.
那么  现在怎么办
So, what now?
现在要做个巫术袋  然后你就跑吧
Now we make a hex bag, and you start running.
如果克劳力找不到你
If Crowley can't find you,
他就不能再召唤别的狗杀你
then he won't be able to sic another mutt on you.
那我不用去地狱了
So I'm not going to hell?
有我在就不会
Not on my watch.
你能先出去一下吗
Will you give us a minute?
当然
Sure.
谢了
Thanks.
迪恩  即使她能躲开克劳力
Dean, even if she can dodge Crowley,
只要艾莉一死  她的灵魂就会进入地狱
as soon as Ellie dies, her soul is earmarked for hell.
除非我们把地狱关上
Not if we shut it down first.
迪恩  你念咒语肯定没用的
The spell's not gonna work for you, Dean.
[咒语]
Kah-nuh-ahm-dahr.
不要紧
Doesn't matter.
我们再找一条地狱之犬  我来杀了它
We'll track down another hellhound, and I'll kill it.
不行
No.
萨姆  我没能通过测试
Sam, I didn't pass the test.
但是我通过了
But I did...
剩下的都让我来
And I'm doing the rest of them.
想得美
My ass you are!
我来关闭地狱之门
I'm closing the gates.
对你来说这无异于自杀
It's a suicide mission for you.
-萨姆  -我也想关上地狱
- Sam... - I want to slam hell shut, too, okay?
但是我想活下来
But I want to survive it.
我想活着  你也应该如此
I want to live, and so should you.
你在这里有朋友  家人
You have friends up here, family.
见鬼  你现在还有自己的房间
I mean, hell, you even got your own room now.
你说得对
You were right, okay?
我还看得到希望
I see light at the end of this tunnel.
我真的很抱歉你看不到
And I'm sorry you don't -- I am.
但希望是有的
But it's there.
如果你和我一起  我就能带你找到希望
And if you come with me, I can take you to it.
萨姆  别傻了
Sam, be smart.
我不傻  你也不傻
I am smart, and so are you.
迪恩  你不是粗人
You're not a grunt, Dean.
你是个天才  在传说方面...
You're a genius -- when it comes to lore, to --
你是我见过的最棒的猎人
You're the best damn hunter I have ever seen --
比我好  比老爸好
Better than me, better than dad.
迪恩  我相信你
I believe in you, Dean.
所以  拜托
So, please --
拜托也请相信我
Please believe in me, too.
[咒语]
Kah-nuh-ahm-dahr.
萨姆
Sam.
小萨姆
Sammy?
萨姆
Sam!
你没事吧
You okay?
我很好  没事
I'm good. I'm okay.
我能行
I can do this.